Guide to the Fred Eggan Papers 1870-1991
University of Chicago Library
- Series X: Photographs
  - Subseries 1: General
    - Annual Bear Ceremony of the Ainu, " Hidakamometsu, Japan, film, [size?], black and white, silent, undated (Located in Box 161), This item has been reformatted for access. (Box 154, Reel 1)
    - South America, map showing culture types, glass slide, undated (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - North America, archaeology, [Indian mound] excavation, prints, negatives [two, including one nitrate], [Fay-Cooper Cole], undated (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - North America, archaeology, grave site, print, undated (Box 154, Folder 3)
    - North America, archaeology, National Park Service, Archaeological Laboratory and Museum, Jamestown, VA, print, undated (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - North America, "Negatives of southwestern album, also Cheyenne, Choctaw, and Wichita, " 4 x 5 negatives, ca.1933 (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - North America, "Negatives of southwestern album, also Cheyenne, Choctaw, and Wichita, " 4 x 5 negatives, ca.1933 (Box 154, Folder 5a)
    - North America, Choctaw, prints, ca.1933 (Box 154, Folder 6)
    - North America, Tsimshian, slides, undated (Box 154, Folder 7)
    - North America, sand design, prints, undated (Box 154, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 2: American Southwest
    - General, Chicago Natural History Museum, kiva stone, print, undated (Box 154, Folder 9)
    - General, KaiDib Film International, petroglyph, slide, undated (Box 154, Folder 10)
    - General, Los Penitentes, prints, 1896 (Box 154, Folder 11)
    - Apache, Papago, Yaqui, via E. W. Haury, archaeological sites, vistas, slides, 1946 (Box 154, Folder 12-13)
    - Navajo, "Mostly Window Rock and Navajo Country, " includes squaw dance, council building, vistas, slides, undated (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - Navajo, portraits, material culture, via Blanche and G. L. Cole, prints, 1901 (Box 155, Folder 2-3)
    - Supai, portrait, print, undated (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - Supai, aerial prints, 1940 (Box 155, Folder 5)
    - Supai, vistas, dance, prints, 1940 (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - Supai, Fred and Dorothy Eggan, Kaboties, candid portraits, prints, undated (Box 155, Folder 7)
    - Supai, portraits, including Don Talayesva, prints, undated (Box 155, Folder 8)
    - Supai, Grand Canyon National Park, Watchtower at Desert View, via Fred Kabotie, postcards, undated (Box 155, Folder 9)
    - Supai, Grand Canyon National Park, "Moencopi Wash, Grand Canyon, " slides, 1955 (Box 155, Folder 10)
    - Supai, including Acoma, prints, undated (Box 155, Folder 11)
    - Supai, including San Ildefonso, Sante Fe Mountains, [Kaboties], slides, 1953 (Box 155, Folder 12)
    - Supai, including Zuni, via Fay-Cooper Cole, prints, ca.1913 (Box 155, Folder 13)
    - Supai, Hopi, pueblo, portrait, prints, undated (Box 155, Folder 14)
    - Supai, Hopi, ritual performance [star clan?], includes "Raymond Firth, Spier, " prints, undated (Box 155, Folder 15)
    - Supai, Hopi, "Canyon del Chelly, our house site, Kabotie paintings, kachina dolls and dancers, close-ups of people, " includes Dorothy Eggan and Taos, slides, undated (Box 155, Folder 16-17)
    - Pueblos, Hopi, "Dorothy's initiation, " includes Don Talayesva, colleagues, prints, ca.1942 (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - Pueblos, Hopi, "Hopi country, " vistas, portraits, slides, 1951 (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - Pueblos, Hopi, "Hopi, sunsets, sheep dip, scenery, Santa Fe Mountains, Canyon del Chelly, " slides, 1952 (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - Pueblos, Hopi, "Sheep dip", prints, undated (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - Pueblos, Hopi, "Hopi Slides to go with talk, " "Clouds, Hopi Buttes, general landscape, Hopi country, sheep dip, " slides, undated (Box 156, Folder 5-7)
    - Pueblos, Hopi, 4 x 5 negatives, 1940 (Box 156, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 3: Southeast Asia
    - Philippines, aerial prints, prints, glass negatives, undated (Box 156, Folder 9)
    - Philippines, "Philippine Islands other than Mountain Province, " slides, undated (Box 156, Folder 10)
    - Thailand, "Bangkok, Nakorn Pathom, " [Fay-Cooper Cole], slides, undated (Box 157, Folder 1-4)
    - Thailand, "Bangkok trip, Canal to Bang Chan, " [Fay-Cooper Cole], slides, undated (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - Thailand, "Chieng Mai, mountain, parasols, temples, " slides, undated (Box 157, Folder 6)
    - Thailand, vicinity of Sukhothai, prints, map, undated (Box 157, Folder 7)
    - Thailand and Cambodia, "Thailand, river trip, Cambodia, Sien Reap Village, Cole, Murdock, Hes, etc. Sien Reap, " [Fay-Cooper Cole, George P. Murdock, E. D. Hester], slides, undated (Box 157, Folder 8)
    - Thailand and Cambodia, "Cambodia, Sien Reap, Angkor, " slides, undated (Box 157, Folder 9)
    - Thailand and Cambodia, "Cambodia, Angkor, " slides, undated (Box 157, Folder 10)
    - Hawaii, return trip, "Hawaii Volcanoes, " slides, ca.1955 (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - Thailand, 35mm negatives, ca.1958 (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - Southeast Asia, unidentified, 35mm negatives, undated (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - Southeast Asia, unidentified, 35mm negatives, undated (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - Southeast Asia, unidentified, 35mm negatives, undated (Box 158, Folder 5)
    - Southeast Asia, unidentified, 35mm negatives, undated (Box 158, Folder 6)
    - Southeast Asia, unidentified, 35mm negatives, undated (Box 158, Folder 7)
    - Southeast Asia, unidentified, 35mm negatives, undated (Box 158, Folder 8)
    - Southeast Asia, unidentified, 35mm negatives, undated (Box 158, Folder 9)
    - Southeast Asia, unidentified, 35mm negatives, undated (Box 158, Folder 10)
    - Southeast Asia, unidentified, 35mm negatives, undated (Box 158, Folder 11)
    - Southeast Asia, unidentified, 35mm negatives, undated (Box 158, Folder 12)
  - Subseries 4: Personal
    - General, postcards, prints, ca.1937 (Box 158, Folder 13)
    - Mexico, prints, ca.1938 (Box 158, Folder 14-15)
    - Mexico, 4x5 negatives, ca.1938 (Box 158, Folder 16)
    - Chicago, portraits, prints, postcard from Kaboties, 1940 (Box 158, Folder 17)
    - Chicago, Southwest, portraits, prints, 1941 (Box 158, Folder 18)
    - Philippines, voyage, contact prints, ca.1950 (Box 158, Folder 19)
    - Philippines, "Voyage home, " slides, ca.1951 (Box 158, Folder 20)
    - Southwest, "Trip home from Southwest, mostly Colorado Mountain shots, " slides, 1951 (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - Unidentified location, family, prints, ca.1952 (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - Southwest, "Grand Canyon, Zion, Bryce, Little Colorado River, " slides, ca.1955 (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - Southwest, "Grand Tetons, Yellowstone, " slides, 1955 (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - Southwest, family, vistas, prints, 1955 (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - Yosemite, slides, 1959 (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - Yosemite, vistas, prints, 1959 (Box 159, Folder 7)
    - Chicago, house, slides, 1959 (Box 159, Folder 8)
    - Chicago, "5602 S. Dorchester, " home interiors, slides, 1959 (Box 159, Folder 9)
    - Chicago, "5602 S. Dorchester, " "House, silver service, " home interiors, slides, ca.1960 (Box 159, Folder 10)
    - Southwest, "Grand Canyon, Little Colorado River, " slides, 1961 (Box 159, Folder 11)
    - Southwest, Colorado, slides, 1962 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Chicago, "1321 E. 50th St., " home interiors, slides, 1965 (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Chicago, Southwest, cityscapes, vistas, slides, ca.1965 (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - Chicago, wedding reception, slides, 1969 (2) (Box 160, Folder 4-5)
    - Joan Eggan, family, slides, 1971 (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - Chicago, "5752 Harper, " exteriors, slides, 1974 (Box 160, Folder 7)
    - Chicago, Fred Eggan portrait, print, undated (as a very young man) (Box 160, Folder 8)
    - Chicago, Fred Eggan portrait, 4x5 negative, undated (Box 160, Folder 9)
    - Chicago, home interiors, prints, undated (Box 160, Folder 10)
    - Chicago, home interiors, negatives, undated (Box 160, Folder 11)
    - Chicago, Hyde Park and University of Chicago, 1 package of strip negatives, undated (Box 160, Folder 12)
    - Hawaii, "Marineland, " slides, undated (Box 160, Folder 13)
    - Hawaii, "Hawaii by Air, Return from the Pacific Science Congress, " slides, undated (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - Southwest, Dorothy Eggan, friends, prints, undated (Box 161, Folder 2)
    - Unidentified portrait, print, undated (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - "Ocean Trip", 4x5 negatives, undated (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - Chicago?, 35mm negatives, undated (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - Negatives for oversized contact sheets found in Subseries 5 (Box 161, Folder 6)
    - Negatives for oversized contact sheets found in Subseries 5 (Box 161, Folder 7)
    - unprocessed negatives (Box 161, Folder 8-10)
  - Subseries 5: Oversized Contact Sheets
    - Item #1, Boboc Mill; Item #2, Beboa, undated (Box 162, Folder 1)
    - Item #3, War Damage, Trip to Bontoc, undated (Box 162, Folder 2)
    - Item #4, Baguio Market; Item #5, Bangued/S.J., undated (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - Item #6, Bokod Valley, undated (Box 162, Folder 4)
    - Item #7 an Item #8, unidentified Southeast Asia, undated (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - Items #9-#11, unidentified American southwest, undated (Box 162, Folder 6)
    - Items #12-#15, unidentified American southwest, undated (Box 162, Folder 7)
- Series XI: Letters of Recommendation
  The material contained in Series XI is restricted and will not be open to researchers until the year 2041.
  - A-F, 1932-1991 (2) (Box 163, Folder 1-2)
  - G-O, 1948-1990 (2) (Box 163, Folder 3-4)
  - P-Z, 1951-1990 (2) (Box 163, Folder 5-6)
  - Philippine Studies Program, personnel file, 1954-1964 (Box 163, Folder 7)
- Series XII: Addendum
  - Subseries 1: Personal
    - Sub-subseries 1: Memorabilia and Miscellaneous Materials
      - Undergraduate Course Book, grade reports and transcripts, 1923-1931 (Box 164, Folder 1)
      - Memorabilia, undated (Box 164, Folder 2)
      - Wedding certificate for Fred Eggan and Joan Rosenfels, 1969 (Box 164, Folder 3)
      - Calendars, 1985-1986 (Box 164, Folder 4)
      - Address book, undated (Box 164, Folder 5)
      - Charts for the Writing of Chinese Characters, 1944 (Box 164, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous Handwritten Notes, undated (Box 164, Folder 7)
      - Notes, undated (Box 164, Folder 8)
      - Notes, undated (Box 164, Folder 9)
      - Notes, undated (Box 164, Folder 10)
      - Clipping- Tuscon Daily Times Re: Roz Spicer, 1991 (Box 164, Folder 11)
      - Clipping, undated (Box 164, Folder 12)
      - Clippings- The Reporter, 1981 (Box 164, Folder 13)
      - Clippings, 1964 (Box 164, Folder 14)
      - Clippings, 1981, undated (Box 164, Folder 15)
      - Christmas Cards, 1983;undated (Box 164, Folder 16)
      - Christmas Cards, 1989 (Box 164, Folder 17)
    - Sub-subseries 2: Posthumous Materials
      - Condolence letters, 1991, undated (Box 164, Folder 23)
      - Condolence Letters for Fred Eggan, 1991 (Box 165, Folder 1)
      - Responses to Condolence Letters, 1991 (Box 165, Folder 2)
      - Condolence Letters for Fred Eggan, 1991 (Box 165, Folder 3)
      - Condolence Letters for Fred Eggan, 1991 (Box 165, Folder 4)
      - Fred Eggan Biographical Information, undated (Box 165, Folder 5)
      - Fred’s Memorial Letters from Friends to Joan, 1991 (Box 165, Folder 6)
      - Fred Eggan, Obituary Clippings, 1991 (Box 165, Folder 7)
      - Fred Eggan’s Last Letter (Unfinished) to Marshall Sahlins, 1991 (Box 165, Folder 8)
      - Condolence Letters, 1991 (Box 165, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, General and Condolences, 1991-1992 (Box 165, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, General and Condolences, 1991 (Box 165, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence to Answer, 1991 (Box 165, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence- Answers, 1991 (Box 165, Folder 13)
      - Personal Correspondence to be Answered, 1991 (Box 165, Folder 14)
  - Subseries 2: Professional
    - Anthropology Student Directory, Autumn, 1980 (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - Anthropology 240, Readings, Part 2, 1948 (Box 166, Folder 2)
    - Anthropology 240, Readings, Part 3, 1948 (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - Syllabi, 1983 (Box 166, Folder 4)
    - Syllabi- T. Pandey, 1979 (Box 166, Folder 5)
    - Anthropology 441 Syllabus, undated (Box 166, Folder 6)
    - Department of Anthropology- Research, etc. 1972-1974 (Box 166, Folder 7)
    - Division of the Social Sciences, Minutes, November 11, 1974 (Box 166, Folder 8)
    - Committee on Southern Asian Studies, 1977 (Box 166, Folder 9)
    - South Asia and Philippine Studies, 1976 (Box 166, Folder 10)
    - Laboratory of Anthropology- Field Trip Fellowships 1929-1934; 1980, undated (Box 166, Folder 11)
    - Anthropology Film Center- Articles of Incorporation, 1975 (Box 166, Folder 12)
    - Anthropology Film Center- Board of Directors, Meeting, Minutes, 1975 (Box 166, Folder 13)
    - Museum of the American Indian, Budget, 1983; 1982 (Box 166, Folder 14)
    - Field Museum- Review of Program, 1974 (Box 166, Folder 15)
    - Malki Museum, undated (Box 166, Folder 16)
    - Anthropology Newsletter, Vol 20 No. 7 September, Vol 20 No. 9, November, 1979 (Box 166, Folder 17)
    - Interagency Archeological Services, undated (Box 166, Folder 18)
    - Handbook of North American Indians, June 1, 1981 (Box 166, Folder 19)
    - The Johnson Foundation, Wingspread, 1971 (Box 166, Folder 20)
    - Advanced Seminar/Hopi, 1980 (Box 166, Folder 21)
    - Philippine Studies Conference, May 28- June 1, 1980 (Box 166, Folder 22)
    - Conference Postings, 1981-1983 (Box 166, Folder 23)
    - Workshop on Gender, Reason and Nuclear Policy, Winter 1989 (Box 166, Folder 24)
    - Daughters of the Desert- Conference Participants, 1985 (Box 166, Folder 25)
    - Symposium, Anthropology on the Great Plains: The State of the Art Plains Conference, October 19-21, 1976 (Box 166, Folder 26)
    - “New Perspectives on the Pueblos”, 1969 (Box 167, Folder 1)
    - American Society for Ethnohistory, Annual Meeting, 1983 (Box 167, Folder 2)
    - Second Philippine Studies International Conference, June 28-30, 1981 (Box 167, Folder 3)
    - University of Nevada, Anthropology Colloquium, undated (Box 167, Folder 4)
    - Fred Eggan- Projects, 1943, 1955, 1959, 1991 (Box 167, Folder 5)
    - The American Academy of Arts and Sciences Bulletin v.33 no 2 (November); v 33. No 5 (February); v. 33 no.6 (March); v.33 no. 8 (May), 1979-1980 (Box 167, Folder 6)
    - American Philosophical Society- Membership, Meetings, 1976 (Box 167, Folder 7)
    - American Philosophical Society- Autumn General Meeting, November 11-12, 1976 (Box 167, Folder 8)
    - American Philosophical Society, for Fall Meeting, 1975 (Box 167, Folder 9)
    - American Philosophical Society, Annual General Meeting, April 24-26, 1975 (Box 167, Folder 10)
    - Memorandum for the Advisory Committee on the Division of Historical Research- Carnegie Institution of Washington, undated (Box 167, Folder 11)
    - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation Fellowships: United States of America and Canada, 1980 (Box 167, Folder 12)
    - Anthropology and the National Academy of Sciences, 1957; 1964-5 (Box 167, Folder 13)
    - National Academy of Science- Delegation to XIII Pacific Science Conference, 1975 (Box 167, Folder 14)
    - National Academy of Sciences- Report on International Biological Program, 1975 (Box 167, Folder 15)
    - National Science Foundation- Nomination Blanks, 1980 (Box 167, Folder 16)
    - Chapter 3- Social Sciences- UNESCO, undated (Box 167, Folder 17)
    - Santa Clara- Historical Preservation Project, 1989-1990 (Box 168, Folder 1)
    - Walpi Project- Adams NEH Application, 1979-1981 (Box 168, Folder 2)
    - Walpi Project- Phase II and III Overview and Summary- Museum of Northern Arizona, Chuck Adams, 1979-1980 (Box 168, Folder 3)
    - Walpi Notes, undated (Box 168, Folder 4)
    - Walpi Project- Phase I- Chuck Adams, 1978 (Box 168, Folder 5)
    - Walpi Project- Phase II Overview and Summary, Fred Eggan Handwritten Notes, 1980 (Box 168, Folder 6)
    - Walpi Exhibition- Zuni Pueblo, 1981 (Box 168, Folder 7)
    - Shusky, Ernest L.- Curriculum Vitae, 1988 (Box 168, Folder 8)
    - Spiro, Melford E.- Curriculum Vitae, 1989 (Box 168, Folder 9)
    - Tedlock, Barbara, 1981 (Box 168, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 3: Correspondence
    - Correspondence- A, 1970, 1980-1984 (Box 169, Folder 1)
    - Annual Meeting- AAA December 3-6, Preceding November 30-December 1st, Claremont Colleges, 1981 (Box 169, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence- B, 1977, 1980-1984, 1987 (Box 169, Folder 3)
    - Briggs, Charles, 1980 (Box 169, Folder 4)
    - British Overseas Airways Corporation- Cargo, 1970 (Box 169, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence- C, 1980-1984 (Box 169, Folder 6)
    - Cellar Book Shop- New Arrivals from the Philippines, undated (Box 169, Folder 7)
    - Coile, Dr. Margaret, Durham, N.C, 1980 (Box 169, Folder 8)
    - Collier, Donald- Letter, 1986 (Box 169, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence- D, 1980-1983, undated (Box 169, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence- E, 1982-1988 (Box 169, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence re: Fred Eggan Dinner, 1982 (Box 169, Folder 12)
    - Evans-Pritchard, E.E. (All Souls Fellowship), 1967-1970 (Box 169, Folder 13)
    - Encyclopedia Brittanica- Compton’s Encyclopedia Revision, 1981 (Box 169, Folder 14)
    - Encyclopedia of the North American Colonies, 1991 (Box 169, Folder 15)
    - Euler, Robert C. Curriculum Vitae, 1980 (Box 169, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence- F, 1980-1984, 1988 (Box 169, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence- Fordham University, 1961-1977 (Box 169, Folder 18)
    - Fortes, Meyer, 1968 (Box 169, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence G, 1980-1981, 1988 (Box 169, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence H, 1979-1984 (Box 169, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence Re: Healing vs. Jones Expert Witness Compensation, 1964 (Box 169, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, Evett D. Hester, February 19-20, 1970 (Box 169, Folder 23)
    - Hickey, Gerald C. 1971, 1991 (Box 169, Folder 24)
    - Hopi Research and Development Co.- Oral History Project, 1979 (Box 169, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence- I, 1983-1984 (Box 169, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence- Inger, Robert F. 1971 (Box 169, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence- J, 1980-1984 (Box 170, Folder 1)
    - Jones, Volney H.- Festschrift, Ann Arbor- “Hopi Ethnohistory”, 1979 (Box 170, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence-K, 1979-1990 (Box 170, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence- L, 1969, 1983, 1987 (Box 170, Folder 4)
    - Levi-Strauss, Claude, 1970 (Box 170, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence- M, 1979-1981 (Box 170, Folder 6)
    - Murphy, Elizabeth- B.A. Paper Draft and Correspondence, 1982 (Box 170, Folder 7)
    - Museum of Northern Arizona Consulting, 1978-1979 (Box 170, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence- Myles, Lisa (Orbis Publishing), 1983 (Box 170, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence-N, 1982-1984 (Box 170, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Nagata, S, 1982-1984 (Box 170, Folder 11)
    - Nims, William H.- Correspondence, 1963 (Box 170, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence- O, 1978, 1984 (Box 170, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence-P, 1979, 1980 (Box 170, Folder 14)
    - Pandey, Triloki, 1980-1984 (Box 170, Folder 15)
    - Parezo, Nancy J. – Louise Lamphere Recap, 1986 (Box 170, Folder 16)
    - Quadrangle Club, 1980 (Box 170, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence-R, 1980-1983 (Box 170, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence- Fred Eggan to Joan Rosenfels (Eggan), 1968-1969 (Box 170, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence- Fred Eggan to Joan Rosenfels (Eggan), 1965-1968 (Box 170, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence- Fred Eggan to Joan Rosenfels (Eggan), undated (Box 170, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence- Fred Eggan to Joan Rosenfels (Eggan), 1966 (Box 170, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence- S, 1960, 1979-1984, 1991 (Box 171, Folder 1)
    - SAR- Program Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 171, Folder 2)
    - Schaafsma, Curtis F- Statement Re: Laboratory of Anthropology, 1981 (Box 171, Folder 3)
    - Shimkin, Demitri- Communication re: Shoshone, Acculturation Papers, 1947, 1979-1980 (Box 171, Folder 4)
    - Silverstein, Michael, 1991 (Box 171, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence- T, 1979-1984 (Box 171, Folder 6)
    - Exhibition- Sol Tax Papers, 1986 (Box 171, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence- U, 1986, undated (Box 171, Folder 8)
    - University of Chicago Library, Special Collections, 1991 (Box 171, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence-V, 1979-1984 (Box 171, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence- W, 1980-1988 (Box 171, Folder 11)
    - Zamora, Mario- Lecture, Los Angeles AAA, 1981 (Box 171, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence- Miscellaneous/Unidentified, 1975-1988 (Box 171, Folder 13)
  - Subseries 4: Writings
    - Eggan, Fred and John M. Stalnaker “American Novelists Ranked” [Reprint], 1929 (Box 172, Folder 1)
    - Eggan, Fred- Tinguian Field Diary, 1934-1935 (Box 172, Folder 2)
    - Eggan, Fred “Historical Changes in The Choctaw Kinship System” [American Anthropologist Reprints], 1937 (Box 172, Folder 3)
    - Eggan, Fred “Some Aspects of Culture Change in the Philippines” [Reprints], 1941 (Box 172, Folder 4)
    - Eggan, Fred and R.F. Barton “Anthropology During the War IX: The Philippines” [American Anthropologist Reprint], 1947 (Box 172, Folder 5)
    - Eggan, Fred “The Philippines and the Bell Report” [Original and Reprint], 1950, 1951 (Box 172, Folder 6)
    - Eggan, Fred “The Philippines and the Bell Report” [Human Organization Reprint], 1951 (Box 172, Folder 7)
    - Eggan, Fred et al- University of Chicago Roundtable “Anthropologists Look at the World Conflict”, 1952 (Box 172, Folder 8)
    - Eggan, Fred “The Ethnological Cultures and their Archeological Backgrounds”, 1952 (Box 172, Folder 9)
    - Eggan, Fred “Social Anthropology and the Method of Controlled Comparison” [Corrections, Correction Sheet, reprint], 1953 (Box 172, Folder 10)
    - Eggan, Fred and Alfredo Pacyaya, “A Sagada Igorot Ballad” [Journal of American Folklore Reprint], 1953 (Box 172, Folder 11)
    - Swadesh, Morris “Time Depths of American Linguistic Groupings” [American Anthropologist Reprints] with Fred Eggan Commentary, 1954 (Box 172, Folder 12)
    - Eggan, Fred “The Philippines Studies Program” and “Some Social Institutions in the Mountain Province and their significance for Historical and Comparative Studies”, 1954 (Box 172, Folder 13)
    - Philippine Social Sciences and Humanities Review [with article by Eggan and Dedication from editor], 1954 (Box 172, Folder 14)
    - Eggan, Fred “Social Anthropology of North American Indian Tribes” and “Social Anthropology: Methods and Results” [Reprints and Copies], 1955 (Box 172, Folder 15)
    - 5th International Congress of Anthropological and Ethnological Sciences- Discussion with Russian Delegation, 1956 (Box 172, Folder 16)
    - Eggan, Fred “Ritual Myths Among the Tinguian” [Journal of American Folklore Reprint], 1956 (Box 172, Folder 17)
    - Eggan, Fred “Glottochronology: A Preliminary Appraisal of the North American Data” [Reprints], 1956 (Box 172, Folder 18)
    - Eggan, Fred “Social Anthropology and the Educational System” [Reprints, Memo, Distribution List], 1957 (Box 172, Folder 19)
    - Eggan, Fred- “Social Structure of the Sagada Igorots” [3rd Copy], undated [1957] (Box 173, Folder 1)
    - Eggan, Fred- “The Ninth Pacific Science Congress”- SSRC Items Reprints, 1958 (Box 173, Folder 2)
    - Eggan, Fred “The Ninth Pacific Science Conference”, 1958 (Box 173, Folder 3)
    - Eggan, Fred and Fay-Cooper Cole “Robert Redfield (1897-1958)” [American Anthropologist Obituary reprint], 1959 (Box 173, Folder 4)
    - Eggan, Fred “An Anthropologist Looks At the Discipline” [Grade Teacher- Article], 1959 (Box 173, Folder 5)
    - Eggan, Fred “The Sagada Igorots of Northern Luzon”, 1960 (Box 173, Folder 6)
    - Eggan, Fred and E.D. Hester “The Povedano Manuscript of 1572” [Reprints from Philippine Studies], 1960 (Box 173, Folder 7)
    - Eggan, Fred and E.D. Hester “The Povedano Manuscript of 1572” [Philippines Studies reprint], 1960 (Box 173, Folder 8)
    - Eggan, Fred “Stanley Stubbs 1906-1959”, [American Anthropologist Obituary Reprint], 1960 (Box 173, Folder 9)